<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My City App</string>
    <string name="temple_name_1">Bhimeshwar Temple</string>
    <string name="temple_name_2">Karkotak Temple</string>
    <string name="temple_name_3">Goluju Temple</string>
    <string name="temple_name_4">Hanuman Garhi Temple</string>
    <string name="temple_name_5">Kainchi Dham Temple</string>
    <string name="temple_desc_1">Named after the powerful Mahabharata character Bhim, Bhimeshwar Mahadev Temple is situated at Bhimtal. According to the Skandpurana, once upon a time Bheem travelled to Himalayas all by himself.</string>
    <string name="temple_desc_2">The Karkotaka Temple also known as Nag Temple situated at the Karkotaka hills are quite well known for the Nag Temple and are visited by thousands of pilgrims who come here to worship the serpent god, Nag Karkotaka Maharaja on the event of Rishi Panchami.</string>
    <string name="temple_desc_3">Ghorakhal means pond of water for horses, it is believed that Golu Dev used to come for a rest here. Incarnation of Lord Shiva Gaur Bhairav or Golu Dev is also know as god of justice. Golu dev use to meet people of his kingdom in his darbar and listen to their problems to resolve in a fair way. At present every year pooja of Golu Dev takes place in the form of the Jagar pooja</string>
    <string name="temple_desc_4">Located on the side of main road between Nakuchiataal to Bhimtaal, parking can be an issue. The temple has a big Hanuman statue, which can be seen from the main road itself. The temple premises is peaceful and quiet.</string>
    <string name="temple_desc_5">Kainchi Dham was established by a great saint Shri Neem Karoli Baba in 1960s at Kainchi village on Nainital-Almora road. It\'s a holy temple and ashram surrounded by hills and trees and a river flowing besides it.</string>
    <string name="restro_name_1">Silver Spoon Restaurant</string>
    <string name="restro_name_2">Singh Restaurant</string>
    <string name="restro_name_3">Machan Restaurant</string>
    <string name="restro_name_4">The Lake Hill Restaurant</string>
    <string name="restro_name_5">Pine Wood Restaurant</string>
    <string name="restro_desc_1">Good food, nice ambience and very well prepared food. Dal makhani and paneer both were delicious. Located at the Watergate hotel, easily accessible by car since it\'s on the main road. Enough parking also available.</string>
    <string name="restro_desc_2">Food was tasty and fresh . Staff is friendly and polite. Loved there Indian food . Garlic naan was great . They personalised the dish as everything was freshly prepared</string>
    <string name="restro_desc_3">One of our favourite Resturants in Bhimtal.Yummy food and owner Akhilesh ji is a very nice person who always greets you with smile and take personal care for your food choices</string>
    <string name="restro_desc_4">Amazing food and lovely ambiance. We had a great time with friends. Staff was really cooperative. Cold coffee was the BEST</string>
    <string name="restro_desc_5">Great food, great view, courteous staff and excellent service. They have multiple seating options including facing the lake</string>
    <string name="lake_name_1">Bhimtal Lake</string>
    <string name="lake_name_2">Garudtal Lake</string>
    <string name="lake_name_3">Saatal Lake</string>
    <string name="lake_name_4">Naukuchiatal Lake</string>
    <string name="lake_desc_1">Bhimtal is a lake in the town of Bhimtal, near Nainital city in Nainital district of Kumaon, India with a masonry dam built in 1883 creating the storage facility. It is the largest lake of Nainital district, as well as Kumaon, which is known as the "Lake district of India"</string>
    <string name="lake_desc_2">Garud Tal is one of the seven lakes of Sattal which are interconnected. The name of these seven lakes is Purna Tal, Ram Tal, Sita Tal, Lakshman Tal, Nal Damyanti Tal, Sukh Tal, and Garud Tal</string>
    <string name="lake_desc_3">A group of pristine mountain lakes nestled within a dense oak forest, Sattal is one of the most stunning of nature\'s gems in Uttarakhand. Lying on the outskirts of Nainital, it makes for a great tourist destination. There are many unexplored spots and trails that can be explored through delightful nature walks.</string>
    <string name="lake_desc_4">Naukuchiatal, or "lake of nine corners", is a small hill station and lake in the Nainital district of Uttarakhand, India. It\'s located 26 kilometers from Nainital and 4 kilometers from Bhimtal</string>
    <string name="cafe_name_1">I heart Cafe</string>
    <string name="cafe_name_2">Belpatra Cafe</string>
    <string name="cafe_name_3">One Bite Cafe</string>
    <string name="cafe_name_4">Kita &amp; Gucchi Cafe</string>
    <string name="cafe_desc_1">We serve the best espresso based drinks in all of Kumaon…our pizzas and snacks are pretty awesome too. So, come on in, oder a drink and some food-enjoy our beautiful cafe with your friends, with a book or with your laptop and some work.</string>
    <string name="cafe_desc_2">Belpatra Cafe &amp; Kitchen is the pioneering offering from Tamohara Hospitality. Nestled in the hills of Uttarakhand, Belpatra takes its name from a Belpatra tree, which finds its place of pride right in the middle of the cafe.</string>
    <string name="cafe_desc_3">One Bite Cafe is a welcoming spot in Bhimtal, Uttarakhand, ideal for a quick bite or a relaxed hangout. Their menu offers a variety of delicious options, perfect for satisfying cravings throughout the day</string>
    <string name="cafe_desc_4">Food was good. Service was quick. Its on main road to mukteswar so easily approachable. Restaurant has ample parking space so one can easily park vehicle.</string>
    <string name="category_1">Lake</string>
    <string name="category_2">Cafe</string>
    <string name="category_3">Restaurant</string>
    <string name="category_4">Temple</string>
</resources>